Jerry J Randolph Apple Valley, CA 92308 jerryjrandolph@gmail.com Cell 760-590-8155 Message 760-447-5034

## **Work Summary**

As a contractor, I was afforded time off between employers. With 12 + Years of Aircraft Maintenance, Modification and Overhaul, my skill set covers Small and Large Aircraft Fixed & Rotor Wing. Boeing 727-767, DC-10, MD-11, Airbus 310, 320, and 380, Sikorsky UH-60, Black Hawks, Boeing CH-47 Chinooks D & F Model, Bell Huey UH-1 Iroquois

### Carrier objective

An inspiring and challenging position in the aircraft maintenance field where my knowledge, education, and experience, can afford me the opportunity for professional and personal growth.

- Phased Unscheduled Line Maintenance, C5 Galaxy Load out Teardown & Buildup
- Serviced, repaired, and overhauled aircraft to ensure airworthiness.
- Read and interpreted manufacturers, and U. S. Army Maintenance manuals, service bulletins, Technical Data, Engineering Data, and other specifications to determine feasibility and method of repairing or replacing malfunctioning or damaged components.
- Performed quality maintenance on aircraft in accordance with (IAW) Original Equipment Manufacturers and Military technical orders as specified.
- Performs miscellaneous duties to service aircraft, including flushing oil systems, cleaning screens, greasing moving parts.
- Performed operationally checks of repaired or modified systems for proper operation.
- Inspected Jet Engines and Components for cracks, corrosion, foreign object damage, burned areas, distortions, security, warping, wear, and missing segments.
- Inspected Jet Engine Turbine Blades to detect cracks, distortion, corrosion, burn-out, security, or breaks.
- Inspected Systems, Sub-Systems, and, Components for proper operation and security.
- Rigged Flight Controls Replaced Damaged Control Tubes, Bell Cranks, Idlers and worn Bearings.
- Troubleshoot malfunctions with Technical Data in aircraft landing gear, flight surfaces and controls, anti-icing, pneudraulic, engines, auxiliary power unit, and ventilation and heating systems.

- Performed 100-hour, progressive, isochronal, phase, periodic, and other hourly or calendar inspections.
- Use of Special tools, Gauges, and Testing Equipment.
- Operation of Fork Lift, Electric Pallet Jack, Overhead Crain and Scamp.

#### **Work Experience**

PAE Barstow/Daggett Army Maintenance Facility Jan 2017 – Jan2019

- Phased, Unscheduled / Line Maintenance
- Sikorsky UH-60 Black Hawk

Tesla Electric Car / PlaneTechs Sept 2016 - Dec 2016

•End of Production Line Maintenance for End of the Quarter Production Quota

Dyncorp International FZ / Nov 2014 – Feb 2016 Dubai UAE (Afghanistan) Boeing CH-47 Chinook D & F Model

- Phased, Unscheduled / Line Maintenance
- C5 Galaxy Load out Teardown & Buildups

Bombardier May 2014 – Sept 2014

- A&P Mechanic Base Maintenance
- CRJ 700/900

Marana Airspace Solutions/ Launch July 7, 2014 – Nov 2014

- A&P Mechanic Line Maintenance
- Boeing 727-767 DC-10, MD 11, 80 Airbus 310, 320

Evergreen/Erickson Helicopter Nov – 2113 – June 2014 McMinnville OR (Afghanistan) AS330J and AS332L

• Flight Manager

RemX/ADI Aug – 2113 Nov – 2113 Palmdale, CA (San Bernardino CA)

Airbus 320 Boeing 727, C-130

• Phased, Unscheduled / Line Maintenance

AECOM Feb – 2013 Aug – 2013 Greensville SC (Afghanistan)

Boeing CH-47 Chinook D & F Model

- Phased, Unscheduled / Line Maintenance
- C5 Galaxy Load out Teardown & Buildup

ATP PRO INC. Dec 2012 – Feb 2113 Jacksonville FL (Long Beach CA)

Piper PA 180, Cessna 150, 172

• Line Maintenance /100 Hour Inspections

Job Aire Group May 2012 – Nov 2012 Phoenix AZ (Victorville CA) Boeing 727, 737, 747,757, 767 DC-10, MD-11 Air Bus A300, 320

• 7, 14, 28, 30, 60, 90, 365 Day Storage Checks

L-3 Vertex Aerospace Communications August 2011 - April 2012 Madison MS (Afghanistan)

Boeing CH-47 Chinook D & F Model

- Phased, Unscheduled / Line Maintenance
- C5 Galaxy Load out Teardown & Buildup

Defense Support Services LLC Dec 2005 – Apri 2010 Greenville SC (Honduras C. A.) Boeing CH-47 Chinook D & F Model

- Phased, Unscheduled / Line Maintenance
- C5 Galaxy Load out Teardown & Buildup

US Airways July 2001-- Nov 2011

• Line Maintenance / A B C D Checks Boeing 727, 737

Tidewater Aviation Academy June 1998 – Oct 1999

- Airframe Class Hands Restoration WWII P51Mustang
- Power Plant Class Hands on Restoration WWII B24 Consolidated Liberator

Georgia Guard January 1991 – January 1992 Savannah GA Boeing CH-47 Chinook

- Phased Maintenance
- Unscheduled / Line Maintenance

U.S. Army December 1979 – December 1982 Lake Hurst NJ Bell Huey UH-1

- Phased Maintenance
- Unscheduled / Line Maintenance

# **Engine Experience**

- Pratt & Whitney PT6, JT8D R-985 Wasp Jr
- Lycoming 235
- Continental IO 360, O 470

#### **Education**

• United States Army Utility and, Cargo Helicopter Repair Schools

- Bell Huey UH-1 Iroquois US Army 67N10
- Boeing CH-47 Chinook US Army 67U20
- Army Maintenance Management System & ULLS-AE
- A&P Certification Tidewater Aviation Academy